welcome to the second beginning tutorial
ยินดีต้อนรับสู่บทแนะนำเริ่มต้นที่สอง
on JavaScript now in the last video I
ใน JavaScript ตอนนี้ในวิดีโอล่าสุด
said we would be using notepad
กล่าวว่าเราจะใช้ Notepad
throughout the series but I kind of
ตลอดทั้งชุด แต่ฉันชนิด
changed my mind because it's a little
เปลี่ยนความคิดของฉันเพราะมันเป็นเพียงเล็กน้อย
bit easier to use notepad plus plus with
ง่ายต่อการใช้
JavaScript now if you want to use
JavaScript ตอนนี้ถ้าคุณต้องการใช้
notepad that's not a problem you can
notepad ไม่ใช่ปัญหาที่คุณทำได้
continue to do that but if you want to
ยังคงทำเช่นนั้น แต่ถ้าต้องการ
use notepad plus plus it's very easy to
ใช้ notepad แถมยังง่ายมาก
download and it's a very quick install
ดาวน์โหลดและติดตั้งได้รวดเร็วมาก
in fact if you open up your browser and
ในความเป็นจริงถ้าคุณเปิดเบราเซอร์ของคุณและ
go to Google and just type in notepad
ไปที่ Google และพิมพ์ใน notepad
plus plus you'll see it comes up very
++ คุณจะเห็นมันขึ้นมามาก
quickly here and you can just hit this
ได้อย่างรวดเร็วที่นี่และคุณก็สามารถกดนี้
download link right here and as I said
ดาวน์โหลดลิงค์ที่นี่และที่ผมพูด
it's a very very quick install now once
เป็นอย่างรวดเร็วติดตั้งตอนนี้อีกครั้ง
you open up notepad plus plus I want you
คุณเปิด Notepad บวกฉันต้องการให้คุณ
to go ahead and copy this template right
ไปข้างหน้าและคัดลอกแม่แบบนี้ถูกต้อง
<here because this is going to be the
ที่นี่เพราะนี่เป็นไป
default template that we'll use
เทมเพลตมาตรฐานที่เราจะใช้
throughout the series and then I want
ตลอดซีรีส์แล้วฉันก็ต้องการ
you to go ahead and save as and then
คุณจะไปข้างหน้าและบันทึกเป็นแล้ว
save it as a HTML document and I just
บันทึกเป็นเอกสาร HTML และฉัน
saved it on my desktop so we'll be
บันทึกไว้บนเดสก์ทอปของฉันดังนั้นเราจะเป็น
reusing this code over and over again
นำรหัสนี้ซ้ำอีกครั้ง
this basic template now as I said in the
แม่แบบพื้นฐานนี้ตามที่ได้กล่าวไว้ใน
last video our JavaScript code goes
รหัสวิดีโอสุดท้ายของเราไปที่ JavaScript